Guide to the Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006 AIS.2006.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Black Political Empowerment Project (B-PEP), 1986-2004; I.
  - Pittsburghers for Open Government, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - People for the American Way, 2004-2007 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Planning Council, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Planning Council, January-February 2006 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Planning Council, October 2006 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Planning Council, November 2006 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Planning Council, February 2007 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Planning Council, March 2007 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Planning Council, July 2007 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Planning Council, August 2007 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Planning Council, December 2007 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Planning Council Action Items, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Planning Council, August 2007 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Planning Council, May 2008 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Planning Council, August 2008 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Planning Council, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Planning Council Additions (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Planning Council Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Planning Council Operations, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Planning Council Meetings Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Position Papers, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Police Consent Decree, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Police Gregory Green, September 2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Police Costa, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Police Jerry Jackson, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Police Jerry Jackson, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Police Jerry Jackson, 2006-2007 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Police, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Police, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 10-12)
  - Police, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Police, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Police, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Police Brutality (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Police Consent Decree Changes, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Police Pamela Lawton, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Posters (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Primary Election Operation Plan, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Public Defender's Office, 2011-2012 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Public Defender's Office Report, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Work Folder, August 2007 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Work Folder, August-September 2007 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Response, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Work Folder, September-October 2007 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Work Folder, 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Summary, October 2007 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Mini-Summit, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Coalition, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Racial Equity and Empowerment Summit Report on EEOC, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Radio, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Reactivation, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Reactivation, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Regional Equity Monitoring Program, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Regional Equity Monitoring Program, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Retreat, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Roll to the Polls, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Ron Daniels, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Schools, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Schools, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Schools, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Schools, Spring 2008 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Schools, Winter 2008 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - School Desegregation, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - School Disparities, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Schools Peal Center, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Schools Right Sizing Plan, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Schools Right Sizing Plan, 2005 (Box 39, Item 1)
  - Schools Right Sizing Plan, 2005-2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Schools Right Sizing Plan, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Schools Schenley, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Schools Schenley, May 2008 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Schools Schenley, June 2008 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Schools Schenley, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Schools Strategic Plan, 2008-2014 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Schools Student Success, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Staff Assisstant, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Staff Assisstant, 2007-2008 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Sustainable Pittsburgh, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Sustainable Pittsburgh 4th Annual Regional Equitable Development Summit, November 2007 (Box 39, Item 2)
  - Sustainable Pittsburgh 5th Annual Regional Equitable Development Summit, December 2008 (Box 39, Item 3)
  - Summit Lists, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Sweatshirt Orders, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Sweatshops, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Sweatshops, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 20-23)
  - Sweatshop Event, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Sweatshops, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Tommy Doswell, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Trophies, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Unions, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Unions, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Urban League of Greater Pittsburgh (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Urban Redevlopment Authority, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Violence Statistics, July 2008 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Voter Citizens Advisory Committee, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Voter Engagement, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Voter Engagement, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Voter Engagement Network Report, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Vote PA, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Voting Information, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Voting Machines Legal Suit, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Voting Machines, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Voting Machines, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Voting Machines, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Voter Protection, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Voter Protection, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Voter Registration, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Voter Registration, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Voting Rights, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
  - Voting Rights (Prisoners), 2005 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Voting Rights Act, 1998-2005 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Voting Rights Act, 2006-2008 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Voting Rights (Katrina), 2005 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Voter Turnout, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Ward Chairs, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Youth & Community (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Youth Outreach/Shotime Pittsburgh, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers (Various), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers on Police Brutality (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers on Tuskegee Airmen, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Posters (Various) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Media History of B-PEP, 2005-2007 (Box 44, Item 1)
- Black and White Reunion, 1997-2005; II.
  This series contains materials relating to the Black and White Reunion, another organization initiated by Stevens. Stevens founded the project in 1997 in the wake of the controversial death of Jonny Gammage at the hands of Pittsburgh police. The organization aimed to build bridges between the African American and Caucasian communities in Pittsburgh. The material in this collection includes brochures, correspondence, flyers, meeting minutes, Stevens' personal notes, news clippings, and other documentation.
  - Brochures and Flyers, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2004, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Enough is Enough, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Grant Proposal, 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Jonny Gammage Scholarship, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Media, 2000-2004, undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, 1997-2001 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, 2002-2003, undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1997-2001 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Men's Lives, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Mural Bridge Project, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - News and Notes, 1998-2004 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Notes, 2000-2004 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Summit Against Racism, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Administrative, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Communications, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - History (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Letterhead (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - MLK Event, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Minutes, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Police, 2006-2008 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2004-2005 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 48-61)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 62-65)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 1-9)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2014-2015 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2006 (Box 42, Item 1)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2007 (Box 42, Item 2-3)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2008 (Box 42, Item 4-7)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2012 (Box 42, Item 8)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2014 (Box 42, Item 9-10)
  - Summit Against Racism, 2015 (Box 42, Item 11)
  - County Proclamation, 2012 (Box 42, Item 12)
  - Web Page, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- NAACP, 1971-2006; 1994-2004; III.
  This series contains materials related to Stevens' leadership in the NAACP. He served as President of the organization from 1994 to 2004, and his decade-long leadership was a very prominent part of Pittsburgh's political and cultural scene. This series is divided into 21 subseries, each reflecting a main focus of the NAACP's efforts. The majority of the files were arranged by subject by Stevens, and the remaining files were arranged in the same manner. This series contains correspondence, brochures, meeting minutes, flyers, memos, notes, agendas, news clippings, and publications.
  - Administrative, 1974-2005; 1.
    This subseries contains material relating to the administrative functions of the NAACP from 1974 to 2005.
    - Accomplishments, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Action Packet, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - African Affairs, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny County Branch Presidents, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Allegheny County Branches, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny- Greensburg, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Article X, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Beaver County Branch, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Benchmarks, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Boycotts, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Branch Building, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Branch Election Procedure, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Branch Information, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Branches, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Brochures, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Lavera, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Building File, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Building Renovation, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Building Renovation, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 20-22)
    - Building Warranties, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Burton, Richard, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Business Cards, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - By-laws, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Campaign, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Campaign, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - City Council Recognition, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Committee Chairs, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Committee Information, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Committee Meeting Schedule, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Committee Reports, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Conflict of Interest Policy, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Constitution and By-laws for Branches, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Consultant, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Convention, 1997-2004 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Convention Policy, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Convention Research, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - County Presidents' Meeting, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Debt, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Effective Meetings, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Election, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 45-47)
    - Election, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Election, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Election Manual, 1998-2004 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Election Misconduct, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Election Notice, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Environmental Enhancement, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Follow-Up, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - General, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - General, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - General, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - General, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Goals for 2002 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Griffin, Andrew, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Harris, Johnifer, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Historic, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - History, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - IBM Model, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Impeachment Process, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Implementation Team, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Individual Position, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Installation Service, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Kendrick, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kingsley Association, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Late Election Material, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Leadership, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Leadership in Tension Situations, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Leadership Training Report, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Marcella, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Letterhead Policy, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Mail, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Mandatory Training, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Manual on Branch Election Procedure, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - McKinney, Marilyn, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Mellon Bank Proposal, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Memos, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Mission Statement, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Mitchem, Henry, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Moss, M. Gayle, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - National, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - National Affairs, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - National NAACP, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - National NAACP Positions, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - National Survey, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Non-Profits, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Office, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Officers, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Officers' Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania NAACP, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Personnel, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Personnel Committee, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh Plan for Action, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Plans for Progress, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Plaques, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Poet, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Presidential Authority, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - President's Memos, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - President's Memos, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - President's Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Proposed Strategic Priorities and Goals, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Public Officials Policy, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Questions and Answers, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Recommendations, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Regional, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Remodeling, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Remodeling, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Resignations, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Resolutions, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Resolutions, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Resolutions, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Resolutions, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Retreat, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Rules of Engagement, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Security, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Shannon, Larry, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - State Information, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - State NAACP, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Strategic Blueprint, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Strategic Planning, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Strategic Planning, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Strategic Planning, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 70-71)
    - Strategic Planning, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Study Guide, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Summits, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Taylor, Randall, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Thalheimer Awards, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Thalheimer Awards, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Urban League, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Vice Chairs, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Volunteers, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - War, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Women in NAACP, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Work File, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Work File, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Work File, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
    - Work File, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6-9)
    - Work File, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10-13)
    - Work File, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14-17)
    - Work File, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Work File, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 19-27)
    - Work File, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Work File, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General, 2004-2006 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Goals for the Future, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Performance Evaluation Angela Howze, May 2004 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Violence, 1994-2005; 2.
    This subseries contains material related to the NAACP's efforts to stop violence in the community, from 1994 to 2005.
    - African American Family Committee, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - African American Family Committee, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Anti-War Movement, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Center for Family Excellence, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Coalition to Counter Hate Groups, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Collaborative Leadership, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Crime Prevention, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Curfew, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Economic Benchmarks, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Gang, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Gang-Peace Summit, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - General, 1995-2001 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - General, 1997-2001 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Hate Crimes, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Mediation, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Mfume, Kweisi, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Peace Bus Initiative, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Recreation Centers, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Stop the Violence, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Strategy 95, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 23-25)
    - Strategy 95, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Strategy 95, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Strategy 95, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 28-31)
    - Strategy 95, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Strategy 95, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 33-35)
    - Strategy 95, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Strategy 95, 1995-2005 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Violence-Free Weekend, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Violence Prevention, 1999-2003 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Violence Prevention Task Force, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 40-42)
    - Violence Prevention Task Force, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 43-44)
    - Wilkinsburg Shootings, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Brother to Brother, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Strategy 95, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Community Involvement, 1990-2004; 3.
    This subseries contains material relating to the NAACP's involvement in the community, from 1990 to 2004.
    - African American Chamber of Commerce, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - African American Cultural Center, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - African American Cultural Museum, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - African American Heritage Parade, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - African American Leadership Directory, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - African American Organizations in Pennsylvania, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Afro-American Heritage Day, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Afro-American Jewish Poetry, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Anheuser-Busch, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Awards and Recognition, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Barrier Breakers, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Black/Jewish Dialogue, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Black Radical Congress, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Byrd, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "Building Peaceful Communities", 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Campaign for African-American Achievement, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Material, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Carlow College, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Children and Youth Services, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Civil Tensions Task Force, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Collaborative Leadership Response, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Community Building, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Community Coordination, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Community Empowerment Association, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Contact Pittsburgh, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Coro Leadership, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Executives, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Curfew, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Day of Atonement, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - East End Neighborhood Forum, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Event Flyers, 1995-2003 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Events, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Fall Jazz Classic, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - The Flavour, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Fox, Alma Speed, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Freedom Corner, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Freedom Unlimited, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - General, 1995-2003 (Box 9, Folder 37-46)
    - General, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - General, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Harris, Charles, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hill District, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hill District Consensus Group, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Hill District Issues, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Jackie, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hunger Services Network, 1994-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Irvis, K. Leroy, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Just Harvest, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kendrick, Hop, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kuumba Trust, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Pittsburgh, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lemington Center, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Maglev, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Make-A-Wish Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Make-A-Wish Foundation, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mentoring, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Million Family March, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - National Conference for Community and Justice, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - National Family heritage Coalition, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - National Philanthropy Day, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Alliance for Democracy, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh's 50 Finest, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - POISE Foundation, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Port Authority, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Race in Pittsburgh, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Salvation Army, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Senior Citizens, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Shuman Center Talent Show, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Spine Line, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Stand for Children, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Thomas Merton Center, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - United Way, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Unity in the Community Day, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Urban League, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Urban League Publications, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Volunteer Possibilities, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Watchful Shepherd, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Working Together Consortium, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Young Black Professionals, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - YWCA, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 44)